Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(Episode 7)
You may have fooled His Highness,
but you can't fool me.
Today,
if you refuse to admit you're pretending...
to have amnesia,
I'll kill this servant.
How dare you test me?
Lu Zhao!
How dare you start a fight here?
Why wouldn't I?
I only wanted to take my time playing this little game...
of cat and mouse with you.
But I've changed my mind.
Aunt.
Go to hell.
She's...
She's dead?
Lu Zhao.
Hhow will you explain this to them?
Nanny, don't be afraid.
I know what to do.
I'll get you out of here.
Your Highness.
You're going on a killing spree here in the manor.
What are you going to do...
about the bodies?
I know what to do.
I know you do.
If we join forces,
we can achieve our goal without bloodshed.
Isn't that better?
The Xuntian Sect...
There's an assassination at King of Chu's manor.
The Xuntian Sect then takes the chance to investigate the manor.
Is this what you mean...
by "joining forces"?
Don't worry.
I'll take care of the aftermath.
I won't let you lose.
Hurry, Your Highness!
Come with me!
Xue Er.
We're at the manor.
Mind your behavior.
Your Highness.
Just come with me.
Mother!
Aunt?
What happened to Aunt?
She died in the back garden...
an hour ago.
What happened?
Aunt.
Aunt!
You wench!
You have the nerve to ask that.
How dare you?
Enough!
Ying Xue.
Your mother passed away.
Why are you hitting me over her death?
Mother told me...
she was meeting you in private today.
But now she's dead.
It's you.
You killed my mother.
It's you!
Ying Xue!
I understand your grief.
Aunt's sudden passing...
saddens me too.
But Aunt was my family.
If she wanted to see me, she could have just said so.
Why would she want to meet in private?
-You... -That's enough.
Lu Zhao.
I've already investigated...
everyone...
in the manor.
Everyone has an alibi.
You're the only exception.
Your Highness.
How can you suspect me?
Not to mention,
I have no reason to harm Aunt.
Furthermore,
I am but a woman.
How could I do such a thing, Your Highness?
Of course, I wouldn't suspect you, my dear.
However,
where were you...
an hour ago?
Is there someone...
who can prove it?
Your Highness, I...
Your Highness.
Xiao Ren, Master of the Xuntian Sect,
has forced his way into the manor with a sword.
What did you say?
I forced my way in, you say?
I heard there was a murder at King of Chu's manor.
I was too eager to help.
What a grand display!
What's this?
Barging into the manor?
Xiao Ren.
Are you rebelling?
There's a murder in the Prince’s manor under the Emperor’s nose.
Can't the Xuntian Sect look into it?
But this is...
family business.
The royal family’s business...
is the nation’s business.
The murderer hasn't been caught yet.
The crisis in the manor hasn't been resolved.
No one is allowed to leave.
Seal off the manor.
Search every inch.
Get a move on.
Xiao Ren!
Don't you dare.
Oversee all officials.
Guard the royal family.
By imperial decree,
execute first, report later.
Those are the Xuntian Sect's duties. Why wouldn't I dare?
But Your Highness,
why are you so afraid we'd investigate?
Could it be...
you're afraid...
I'll uncover some disgraceful secret in the manor?
We've looked into it.
She's the murderer!
My mother only met her before she died.
It must be her.
I didn't do it.
I didn't.
You are...
a suspect?
If that's the case,
why don't I...
take her with me,
and I'll interrogate her properly?
Xiao Ren.
She is my wife.
How dare you touch her?
This is the Princess of Chu?
My apologies.
I just thought that...
this lady with the beautiful clothes...
was the Princess instead.
If I may be so bold,
who are you?
I am Her Highness' cousin.
You accused Her Highness of obstructing official duties.
Ling Su.
Take her away.
I'm not going!
Your Highness!
Your Highness, save me!
Report!
Madam Fang's bodyguards...
and housekeeper...
have been found.
Bring them here.
They are all dead.
Judging by the knife wounds,
it was the work of the Xuntian Sect.
You wretched woman.
You will die with my mother!
Watch your mouth.
Your mother...
fell into the pond and drowned.
How dare you slander Her Highness?
Your Highness!
A servant reported...
that Madam Fang had too much to drink,
and she fell into the water and drowned.
She is just a commoner.
Master Xiao.
Are you going to...
seal off my manor...
and take away my wife because of this?
If word gets out,
aren't you afraid of gossip?
You're right, Your Highness.
Since this is their family matter,
it is not appropriate for the Xuntian Sect...
to get involved.
However,
Your Highness,
you have committed too many evil deeds.
You should watch out for retribution.
I'll take my leave.
By the way,
there's no need to rush, Your Highness.
I'm taking my time as well.
Let's play this game slowly.
Thank you for protecting me, Your Highness.
Actually,
the truth will speak for itself.
I could've gone to the Xuntian Sect with them.
It's not as simple as you think.
Jin Lin.
Take the Princess back to her room.
Your Highness.
Go.
Please come this way, Your Highness.
Why?
Why do you treat me like this?
It was my mother who died.
It was my mother.
Didn't I tell you...
not to cause any more trouble?
You colluded with your mother...
to make things difficult for Lu Zhao.
But you ended up attracting those Xuntian Sect mad dogs.
Fang Yuan Rou is nothing.
Lu Zhao killed her, you say?
What a joke.
The guards and women with her...
were all killed by the Xuntian Sect.
Do you know that?
Xue Er.
The Xuntian Sect has been after me.
They killed your mother...
so that they can search my manor...
under the guise of an investigation.
If they succeed,
me,
you,
and over 300 lives in the manor...
will all go to hell...
with your stupid mother.
Your Highness.
I was wrong.
I won't cause trouble again.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
I'll be obedient from now on.
You're grounded from now on.
Without my permission,
you can't go anywhere.
Your Highness!
Chief.
Why are you dressed so extravagantly?
You wouldn't understand.
You're here.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I've been watching Situ Xian.
Did he believe it?
Yes.
He buried the guards and the madam hastily.
This was to confirm they fell into the water and died.
What happened today...
was all thanks to you.
Thank you.
We're allies.
No need to thank me.
Then in the future,
what if...
I want to kill someone else?
In that case,
I will surely...
pass you a good knife.
What's this?
This is the roast goose from the imperial kitchen.
I just...
brought it with me.
Try it.
Is it good?
If it's good, I'll grab some for you next time.
It's the middle of winter.
Freshly roasted goose...
gets cold quickly.
No matter how good the skill,
it's bound to taste fishy.
From the palace to Prince of Chu's manor,
even a fast horse needs an hour to travel the distance.
However, this roast goose is still hot.
How did you manage to "just bring it" with you?
You must have specially brought it here.
You rode fast on a swift horse,
and you used a charcoal stove to keep it warm.
The plate is still hot to touch.
Master Xiao, you sure are attentive.
Could it be...
that you like me?
What if I say yes?
What will you do?